Finding Aid for American Society for Information Science and Technology Records, 1925-2001
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- CHAPTERS
  - Individual Chapters
    - Florida
      - Financial, 1991-1993 1995-1998, 3 folders (Box 46)
      - General, 1966-1978 19891992-1993, 4 folders (Box 46)
    - Four Corners, 1980 (Box 46)
    - Frontier
      - Annual Reports, 1973-74 (Box 46)
      - Constitution, 1972 and undated (Box 46)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1978, 3 folders (Box 46)
      - Financial Reports, 1972-1977 (Box 46)
      - Meeting Notices, 1972-1974 (Box 46)
      - Minutes, 1972 (Box 46)
      - Newsletters, 1972-1975 (Box 46)
      - Officers, 1972-1974 (Box 46)
      - Petitions, 1971-1972 (Box 46)
    - Georgia
      - Annual Reports, 1980-1983 (Box 46)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box 46)
      - Financial Reports, 1981-1985 and 1993, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - Meeting Notices, 1980-1983 (Box 46)
      - Minutes, 1980-1984 (Box 46)
      - Newsletters, 1980-1983 (Box 46)
      - Officers, 1980-1983 (Box 46)
      - General, 1984-1989 1992, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Indiana
      - Annual Reports, 1976-1980 (Box 46)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1984-1985 (Box 46)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1980 (Box 46)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1980, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - Financial, 1970-1986 1991-1993 1995-1999, 4 folders (Box 46)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1969-1983 (Box 46)
      - Minutes, 1968-1981 (Box 46)
      - Miscellanea, 1969-1984 (Box 46)
      - Newsletters, 1975-1986, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - Officers, 1962-1982 (Box 46)
      - General, 1982-1995, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Los Angeles
      - Annual Reports, 1968-1980 (Box 47)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1977-1987 1988-1989, 6 folders (Box 47)
      - Conference: "Quantifying Quality," 1977 (Box 47)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1984, 4 folders (Box 47)
      - Financial Reports, 1967-1986 and 1991-1999, 8 folders (Box 47)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1962-1986 (Box 47)
      - Membership Directories, 1971-1974 (Box 47)
      - Minutes, 1980 (Box 47)
      - Miscellanea, 1966-1982 (Box 47)
      - Newsletters, 1961-1986, 4 folders (Box 47)
      - Officers, 1983-1985 (Box 47)
      - Petitions to Form the Chapter, 1961 (Box 47)
      - General, 1985-1997, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Louisiana, 1974-1976 (Box 48)
    - Metropolitan New York
      - Annual Reports, 1971-1980 (Box 48)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1976-1982, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - Correspondence, 1959-1984, 3 folders (Box 48)
      - Financial, 1971-1986 1991-1999, 4 folders (Box 48)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1960-1982, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - Minutes, 1964-1984 (Box 48)
      - Newsletters, 1963-1982 (Box 48)
      - Officers, 1961-1983 (Box 48)
      - General, 1985-1996 (Box 48)
    - Mexico, 1980 (Box 48)
    - Miami, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Michigan
      - Annual Reports, 1976-1981 (Box 48)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1980 (Box 48)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1985 (Box 48)
      - Financial, 1970-1985 1987 1991-1999, 4 folders (Box 48)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1972-1982 (Box 48)
      - Minutes, 1970 (Box 48)
      - Newsletters, 1972-1982 (Box 48)
      - Officers, 1969-1981 (Box 48)
      - General, 1984-1985 1991-1993 (Box 48)
    - Minnesota
      - Annual Reports, 1968-1984 (Box 48)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1984-1985 (Box 48)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1982, 3 folders (Box 48)
      - Financial
        - Financial Reports
          - 1971-1996, 3 folders (Box 48)
          - 1997-1999, 1 folder (Box 49)
        - Treasurer's Records: annual financial reports, receipts, bank statements, copies of cancelled checks, treasurer's reports and correspondence
          - Bills and Related Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 49)
          - Chapter Income Statement, 1993 (Box 49)
          - Chapter Officer's Manual, 1992 (Box 49)
          - Ledgers, 1973-1985 (Box 49)
          - General, 1981-1994, 11 folders (Box 49)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1970-1981 (Box 49)
      - Membership Directory, 1972 1975, 2 folders (Box 49)
      - Minutes, 1970-1982 (Box 49)
      - Newsletters
        - 1968-1981, 12 folders (Box 49)
        - 1981-1984, 3 folders (Box 50)
      - Officers, 1968-1982 (Box 50)
      - Petitions to Establish, 1968 (Box 50)
      - General, 1983-1988 1992-1993 1995, 3 folders (Box 50)
    - Missouri, 1974-1978 (Box 50)
    - New England
      - Annual Reports, 1969-1985 (Box 50)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1984-1987, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1985, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Financial, 1965-1986 1991-1999, 4 folders (Box 50)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1972-1987 (Box 50)
      - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 50)
      - Newsletters, 1974-1986 (Box 50)
      - Officers, 1965-1985 (Box 50)
      - General, 1985-1989 1991-1997 (Box 50)
    - New Jersey
      - Chapter of the Year, 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Correspondence, 1975 1985-1987 (Box 50)
      - Financial, 1991-1998, 4 folders (Box 50)
      - Membership Directory, 1988 (Box 50)
      - General, 1985-1992, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Northern Europe (or North European) (Box 51)
      - Financial, 1973-1984 and 1993, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Northern Ohio
      - Annual Reports, 1972-1978 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Bylaws, 1964 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Chapter of the Year, 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Correspondence, 1964-1985, 5 folders (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Directories, 1982-1983 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Financial, 1965-1985 1991-1999, 4 folders (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Meeting Announcements, 1963-1984 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Minutes, 1965-1979 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Newsletters, 1966-1985, 4 folders (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Officers, 1969-1984 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Press Clippings, 1975 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Northern Ohio-Pittsburgh Continuing Education Seminars, 1964-1975 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - General, 1984-1986 1988-1989 1992-1993 1995 (Box 51 (cont.))
    - Ohio Chapters Joint Activities, 1968-1982, 2 folders (Box 51 (cont.))
    - Oklahoma
      - Annual Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Directory, 1984 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Financial, 1983-1984 1986 1992 (Box 51 (cont.))
    - Pacific Northwest
      - Annual Reports, 1974-1984 (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Chapter of the Year, 1976-1979, 3 folders (Box 51 (cont.))
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1986 (Box 52)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1985, 4 folders (Box 52)
      - Directory, 1971-1972 (Box 52)
      - Financial, 1974-1986 1991-1999, 5 folders (Box 52)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1973-1986 (Box 52)
      - Minutes, 1976-1982 (Box 52)
      - Miscellanea, 1981-1984 (Box 52)
      - Newsletters, 1972-1986, 7 folders (Box 52)
      - Officers, 1964-1984 (Box 52)
      - Seminar: "The World of Computers...," 1978 (Box 52)
      - General, 1985-1989 1991-1992 1994-1995 (Box 52)
    - Pittsburgh
      - Annual Reports, 1975-1981 1995 (Box 52)
      - Bylaws, undated (Box 52)
      - Correspondence, 11961-1984, 4 folders (Box 52)
      - Financial, 1971-1985 1991-1998, 5 folders (Box 52)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1973-1981 (Box 52)
      - Miscellanea, 1976-1982 (Box 52)
      - Newsletters, 1971-1980 (Box 52)
      - Officers, 1973-1983 (Box 52)
      - General, 1980 1985 1987 1988 1992-1993 1995 (Box 52)
    - Potomac Valley
      - Annual Reports, 1969-1973 (Box 52)
      - Chapter of the Year
        - 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 52)
        - 1983-1987 1989, 5 folders (Box 53)
      - Conference, 1970 "Innovations in Communications" (Box 53)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1967 and undated (Box 53)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1985, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Financial, 1970-1986 1991-1999, 5 folders (Box 53)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1965-1984, 3 folders (Box 53)
      - Membership, 1963-1975 (Box 53)
      - Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
      - Miscellanea, 1959-1979 (Box 53)
      - Newsletters, 1969-1986, 3 folders (Box 53)
      - Officers, 1960-1970 (Box 53)
      - Press Releases, 1975-1980 (Box 53)
      - Seminar-Second East Coast Instant Information Seminar and Exhibits, 1977 (Box 53)
      - Workshop: Computer Controlled Photocomposition and Automatic Typesetting, 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - General, 1983-1989 1992-1995 (Box 53)
    - San Diego
      - Meeting Announcements, 1961-1979 (Box 53)
      - General, 1961-1980 (Box 53)
    - San Francisco
      - Annual Reports, 1969-1978 (Box 54)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1961 (Box 54)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1980 (Box 54)
      - Financial, 1966-1985 1991-1996, 3 folders (Box 54)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1961-1979 (Box 54)
      - Membership Directories, 1968-1974 (Box 54)
      - Officers, 1962-1981 (Box 54)
      - General, 1981-1987 1991-1993 1995 (Box 54)
    - South Texas, 1963-1968 (Box 54)
    - Southern Ohio (SOASIS)
      - Annual Reports, 1973-1984, 4 folders (Box 54)
      - Award Information, 1977 and 1981 (Box 54)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1975-1983, 7 folders (Box 54)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1963-1974 (Box 54)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1983, 4 folders (Box 54)
      - Financial, 1966-1986 1991-1999, 4 folders (Box 54)
      - Guidelines for Officers and Committees, 1981 (Box 54)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1967-1985 (Box 54)
      - Membership, 1980 (Box 54)
      - Minutes, 1964-1983 (Box 54)
      - Miscellanea, 1969-1970 (Box 54)
      - Newsletters, 1973-1984, 8 folders (Box 55)
      - Officers, 1963-1982 (Box 55)
      - Press Releases, 1976-1978 (Box 55)
      - Seminar-The Impact of Human Cybernetics of Information Science, 1977 (Box 55)
      - Symposium-Information: A Resource for Professionals, 1967 (Box 55)
      - Tear Sheets, 1976-1980 (Box 55)
      - General, 1984-1993 1995 (Box 55)
    - Southern U.S.
      - Financial, 1991-1992 (Box 55)
      - General, 1976-1986 1989 1991 1992, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Taipei
      - Correspondence, 1981-1989, 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Miscellaneous Publications, 4 folders (Box 55)
      - Financial, 1991-1993 1996 and 1998, 3 folders (Box 55)
      - Seminar on Optical Disk System: Information Technology, 1988, 3 folders (Box 55)
      - Volume of Translations of Selected Materials, 1987 (Box 55)
      - General, 1984-1995, 3 folders (Box 55)
        (also includes Taipei Area Student Chapter materials)
    - Texas
      - Annual Reports, 1974-1985 (Box 55)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1978-1979 (Box 55)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1974 (Box 55)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1981, 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Financial, 1975-1986 1991-1998, 5 folders (Box 55)
      - Meeting Notices, 1973-1985 (Box 55)
      - Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 55)
      - Newsletters, 1975-1985, 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Officers, 1974-1980 (Box 55)
      - General, 1984-1986 1988-1989 1991-1993 1995 (Box 55)
    - United Kingdom, 1980 (Box 56)
    - Upstate New York
      - Annual Reports, 1969-1978 (Box 56)
      - Calendar of Meetings, 1980-1982 (Box 56)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1982, 2 folders (Box 56)
      - Financial Reports, 1966-1984 and 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 56)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1967-1985 (Box 56)
      - Membership, 1965-1979 (Box 56)
      - Minutes, 1963-1977 (Box 56)
      - Miscellanea, 1970-1977 (Box 56)
      - Newsletters, 1969 and 1982-1984 (Box 56)
      - Officers, 1963-1978 (Box 56)
      - General, 1981-1989 1992-1993 (Box 56)
    - Western Canada
      - Annual Meeting Programs, 1974-1980 (Box 56)
      - Annual Reports, 1971-1978 (Box 56)
      - Bylaws, 1976 (Box 56)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1981, 7 folders (Box 56)
      - Financial, 1970-1983 1991-1996 and 1998, 5 folders (Box 56)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1969-1981 (Box 56)
      - Membership, 1979 (Box 56)
      - Newsletters, 1968-1975 (Box 56)
      - Officers, 1979-1984 (Box 56)
      - Proceedings of Annual Meeting, 1971 1987 1989-1990, 4 folders (Box 56)
      - Questionnaire, 1974 (Box 56)
      - General, 1981 1986 1988-1989 1992 1993 1995 1997 (Box 56)
    - Wisconsin
      - Annual Reports, 1977-1982 (Box 56)
      - Constitutions and Bylaws, 1973-1974 (Box 56)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1982, 3 folders (Box 56)
      - Financial, 1973-1985 1991-1998, 5 folders (Box 56)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1976-1982 (Box 56)
      - Minutes, 1973-1981 (Box 56)
      - Newsletters, 1980-1983 (Box 56)
      - Officers, 1974-1983 (Box 56)
      - General, 1980 1985-1986 1988 1992 1993 1995 1999 (Box 56)
    - Student Chapters
      - Atlanta, 1983 (Box 56)
      - C. W. Post University, 1976-1982 (Box 56)
      - California State University, Fullerton, 1976-1977 (Box 56)
      - Capitol Area (Catholic University), 1988-1989 (Box 56)
      - Case Western Reserve University, 1966-1978 (Box 56)
      - Central New York, 1976-1982 (Box 56)
      - Columbia University, 1964-1981 1988 (Box 56)
      - Drexel University, 1964-1983 1988 (Box 56)
      - East Texas State University, 1975-1983 (Box 57)
      - Emory University, 1977 (Box 57)
      - Florida State University, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
      - Indiana University, 1967-1971 1988-1989 (Box 57)
      - Kent State University, 1974-1984 (Box 57)
      - Long Island University, 1977-1978 1988 (Box 57)
      - Louisiana State University, 1975-1979 (Box 57)
      - Nashville University Center, 1970-1976 (Box 57)
      - National Capitol Area, 1967-1984 (Box 57)
      - New Jersey, 1983 (Box 57)
      - Northern Texas, 1981-1984 (Box 57)
      - Pratt Institute, 1970 (Box 57)
      - Queens College, 1976 (Box 57)
      - Rosary College, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
      - Rutgers University, 1964-1970 1988-1989 (Box 57)
      - St. John's University, 1971-1983 (Box 57)
      - San Jose State University, 1982-1983 (Box 57)
      - Simmons College, 1975-1985 (Box 57)
      - State University of New York at Albany, 1973-1984 (Box 57)
      - Syracuse University, 1976-1983 (Box 57)
      - Taipei Area, 1984-1985 1988-1989, 3 folders (Box 57)
      - Texas Woman's University, 1981-1983 (Box 57)
      - UCLA, 1976-1983 1988 (Box 57)
      - University of Alberta, 1976-1980 (Box 57)
      - University of Arizona, 1976-1978 1990-1991 (Box 57)
      - University of Chicago, 1984 (Box 57)
      - University of Cincinnati, 1974-1975 (Box 57)
      - University of Dayton, 1968 (Box 57)
      - University of Denver, 1973-1982 (Box 57)
      - University of Hawaii, 1979-1982 (Box 57)
      - University of Illinois, 1977-1982 1988 (Box 57)
      - University of Louisville, 1977 (Box 57)
      - University of Michigan, 1973-1982 1988 (Box 57)
      - University of Minnesota, 1979-1982 (Box 57)
      - University of Mississippi, 1982 (Box 57)
      - University of Missouri, 1977 (Box 57)
      - University of Oklahoma, 1975-1986 (Box 57)
      - University of Oregon, 1977 (Box 57)
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1966-1978 (Box 57)
      - University of South Carolina, 1977 (Box 57)
      - University of Southern California, 1981-1982 (Box 57)
      - University of Southwestern Louisiana, 1976 (Box 57)
      - University of Tennessee, 1982-1984 (Box 57)
      - University of Texas, Austin, 1976-1977 (Box 57)
      - University of Wisconsin, Madison, 1976 1988-1989 (Box 57)
      - University of Wisconsin, Milwaukee, 1982-1984 1988 (Box 57)
      - Wayne State University, 1979 (Box 57)
      - Western Michigan University, 1978 (Box 57)
- SPECIAL INTEREST GROUPS
  The SPECIAL INTEREST GROUPS series (13 linear feet) documents those professional societies within ASIS devoted to the special interests of a portion of the membership. Each group (or SIG) holds a franchise from the parent society and meets annually with ASIS. They also hold their own meetings at varying intervals. For information on the basic role of each Special Interest Group the researcher should consult the folder labeled "Profiles", in which there are brief descriptions of each SIG in existence at the time the list was created. The following are Special Interest Groups for which we have information. (As society and research trends shift over time, new SIGs begin and older SIGs are disbanded, so the researcher is urged to look beyond this list.)
  List of some of the ASIS Special Interest Groups:
  ACT--Advanced Communications Techniques
  AH---Arts and Humanities
  ALP--Automated Language Processing
  AOF--Automated Office of the Future, in 1984 the name was changed to OIS
  BC---Biological and Chemical Information Systems
  BSS--Biological and Social Sciences
  CAS--Computers and Society
  CBE--Cost, Budgeting and Economics
  CIS--Computer Information Services
  CR---Classification Research
  CRS--Computerized Retrieval Services see also SDI
  ED---Education for Information Science
  EEI--Energy and Environment Information
  FIS--Foundations of Information Science
  IAC--Information Analysis Center, name changes to IAE in 1978
  IAE--Information Analysis Evaluation, formerly IAC
  IGP--Information Generation and Publication
  III--International Information Issues
  IP---Information Publishing
  IRM--Information Resources Management
  ISE--Information Services to Education
  LAN--Library Automation Networks
  LAW--Law and Information Technology
  MED--Medical Information Systems
  MGT--Management of Information Activities
  NDB--Numeric Data Bases
  NMR--Non-Print Media and Reprographics; see also SRT
  NPM--Non-Print Media
  PPI--Public-Private Interface
  PUB--Publication
  RIS--?
  RT---Reprographic Technology
  SDI--Selective Dissemination of Information, name changes to CRS in 1975
  SRT--Storage and Retrieval Technology, formerly NMR
  TIS--Technology, Information and Society
  UOI--User On-Line Interaction
  WEP--Writing, Editing, Publishing
  Researchers interested in SIG/ED should also examine the Education Committee files in the Committees series. In addition, the Awards series contain further information on the Doctoral Forum.
  - Administration, 1981 1984 1986 1988 1991 (Box 58)
  - Advisory Committee, undated (Box 58)
  - Affiliate Membership, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Annual Business Meeting, 1967 1977-1978 1981-1985, 5 folders (Box 58)
  - Annual Meeting, 1976-1980, 3 folders (Box 58)
    (includes combinations of contributed papers, evaluations, and pre-and post-conference procedures)
  - Applications, 1967 and undated (Box 58)
  - Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 58)
  - Bylaws (Model), 1969-1982, 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Cabinet Councilor, 1976-1981 Annual Reports (Box 58)
  - Cabinet Director (Box 58)
  - Cabinet Director Elections, 1987 (Box 58)
  - Cabinet Meetings
    - Agenda, 1960-1985 (Box 58)
    - Minutes, 1966-1985 1989-1995, 9 folders (Box 58)
  - Cabinet Members, 1966-1967 (Box 58)
  - Cabinet Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 59)
  - Cabinet Steering Committee, 1975-1995, 7 folders (Box 59)
  - Checklist for Deadlines, undated, 1968 and 1982-1985 (Box 59)
  - Classification Research Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 59)
  - Conference, 1981 (Box 59)
  - Correspondence
    - 1965-1984 1986-1994, 20 folders (Box 59)
    - 1995-1996 1997-1998 1999 (Box 60)
  - "The Essence of SIGs" by Robert S. Tannehill, Jr. (Box 60)
  - Dissolution Process, 1991 (Box 60)
  - Financial Information
    - Budget Form, blank, 1986 (Box 60)
    - Budgets, 1981 1983-1984 1986, 3 folders (Box 60)
    - Financial Policy, 1971-1975 (Box 60)
    - Financial Reports
      - 1966-1989, 25 folders (Box 60)
      - 1990-1998, 8 folders (Box 61)
    - Funding, 1968-1981 (Box 61)
    - General, 1992-1993 (Box 61)
  - Formation, Merger and Dissolution of SIGs (Box 61)
  - Headquarters Bulletin, 1972 (Box 61)
  - Long Range Planning Report, 1978-1982 (Box 61)
  - Membership, 1966-1984 1991 1993, 3 folders (Box 61)
  - Memo, 1970 1973-1985, 8 folders (Box 61)
  - Mid-Year Meeting, 1980 (Box 62)
  - Motions, 1976-1981 (Box 62)
  - Newsletter, 1974-1976 1986-19891991, 5 folders (Box 62)
  - Officers
    - General, 1968-1986, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Job Descriptions, 1980 and undated (Box 62)
    - Manual
      - Manual, 1967 1976 1979, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Correspondence, 1967 1976 1997, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Roster Form, blank, 1988 (Box 62)
    - Rosters, 1970-1980 (Box 62)
    - Workshop
      - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 62)
      - Correspondence and Minutes, 1969-1976 (Box 62)
  - Pathfinders, 1976-1978 (Box 62)
  - Procedures, 1973 and 1979 (Box 62)
  - Profiles, 1972-1982 and undated (Box 62)
  - Project and Reserve Fund
    - Correspondence
      - 1971-1981, 4 folders (Box 62)
      - 1983-1988 1991 1993-1995, 5 folders (Box 63)
    - Electronic Mail System, undated (Box 63)
    - Feedback, 1971 (Box 63)
    - Financial Information, 1970-1974 (Box 63)
    - Grant Application Forms, blank, undated (Box 63)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1971-1976 (Box 63)
  - Proto-SIG: "Computing Literature and Resource Management: A Directory," 1982 (Box 63)
  - Publications, 1967-1972 1984 1990 (Box 63)
  - Reports, 1966-1986 1994, 2 folders (Box 63)
  - SIG/CON, 1977-1979 1983-1984 1988 1995 (Box 63)
  - SIG of the Year, 1977-1983 1990-1991, 6 folders (Box 63)
  - SIG Publication of the Year, 1991 (Box 63)
  - Statement of Purpose, undated (Box 63)
  - Steering Committee, 1977-1981 (Box 63)
  - Study Group, 1975-1976 (Box 63)
  - Subject Index to SIGs and Meeting Planning Guide, 1993-1994 (Box 63)
  - Survey: "Manpower Requirements of Information Science," 1976-1978 (Box 63)
  - Task Force on SIGs (Ad Hoc), 1975-1976 [1981-1983 ?], 1987, 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Tri Society Meeting (ACS, ASIS, and SLA) Progress Report, 1978-1984 (Box 63)
  - Wish List, 1989 (Box 63)
  - Individual SIGs
    - Purpose, undated (Box 63)
    - ACT (Advanced Communications Techniques), 1978 (Box 63)
    - AH (Arts and Humanities)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1983, 5 folders (Box 63)
      - Newsletters, 1968-1983 (Box 63)
      - General, 1988-1995, 3 folders (Box 63)
    - ALP (Automated Language Processing)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1985, 2 folders (Box 64)
      - General, 1989 1993-1995, 2 folders (Box 64)
      - Newsletters, 1967-1981 (Box 64)
    - AOF (Automated Office of the Future)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1983, 2 folders (Box 64)
      - Newsletters, 1980-1985 (Box 64)
    - BC (Biological and Chemical Information Systems)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1984, 5 folders (Box 64)
      - Newsletters, 1974-1984, 2 folders (Box 64)
      - General, 1980-1993, 6 folders (Box 64)
    - BSS (Biological and Social Sciences)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1967-1975 (Box 64)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1981, 6 folders (Box 64)
      - Dissolution Survey, 1985 (Box 64)
      - Newsletters, 1967-1982, 2 folders (Box 64)
      - General, 1988-1994, 3 folders (Box 64)
    - CAS (Computers and Society), 1969 (Box 65)
    - CBE (Cost, Budgeting and Economics)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1979, 4 folders (Box 65)
      - Minutes, 1970-1979 (Box 65)
      - Newsletters, 1971-1977 (Box 65)
    - CIS (Community Information Services)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1983, 2 folders (Box 65)
      - Newsletters, 1977-1980 (Box 65)
    - CR (Classification Research)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1968-1974 (Box 65)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1984, 5 folders (Box 65)
      - Newsletters, 1967-1985 1989, 3 folders (Box 65)
      - Proposals, 1981 (Box 65)
      - Technical Publications, 1980 (Box 65)
      - Terminology Project, 1976-1978 (Box 65)
      - Workshop Proceedings, 1990 (Box 65)
      - General, 1989-1995, 2 folders (Box 65)
    - CRS (Computerized Retrieval Services)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1985 1991-1994, 2 folders (Box 65)
      - Newsletters, 1975-1984 (Box 65)
    - ED (Education for Information Science)
      - Business Meeting Minutes, 1976-1980 (Box 65)
      - Bylaws, 1973 and 1975 (Box 65)
      - Careers Brochure, 1978-1982 (Box 65)
      - Conference Proceedings of the Curriculum Committee on Education in Information Science, undated, 2 folders (Box 65)